Toggle navigation [](https://smoner.com/)

Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

smoner.com Focus on user privacy, our commitment to data protection.At smoner.com our first priority is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains the types of information collected and recorded by smoner.com and the methods we use if you have additional questions. Or need more information about our privacy policy, do not hesitate to contact us.In order to extend protection to the privacy and rights of our clients and site visitors, we have created a Privacy Policy that sets forth what information smoner.com collects on visitors and what is done with the collected information. This Privacy Policy directs the way in which we collect, use, maintain and disclose information gathered from users of this website

**Information**

Personal information collected through our website may be used to contact users and notify them about the products and services offered by smoner.com and trusted affiliates, independent contractors and partners. Business And to improve the user experience with smoner.com and our affiliates, independent contractors and business partners The user database of smoner.com will not be sold to any legal entity for marketing purposes or mailing lists. Personal information will not be sold or transferred to our business partners without our prior consent. However, when in our good faith judgment We have a duty to do it under relevant laws. We will disclose information collected to third parties.

**Log file**

smoner.com follows the standard steps of using these log files to record visitors when visiting all hosting companies' websites. Do this and be part of the hosting service analysis. The information collected by the log file consists of the Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), stamp page, date and time, reference / exit, and clicks. These are not linked to any personal information. The purpose of the data is to analyze trends, look at websites, track user movements on the website, and collect demographic information.

**Cookies and web beacons**

smoner.com uses the same cookies as other websites. These cookies are used to store information including visitor preferences and web pages on websites that visitors visit or visit. Information used to improve the user experience by customizing the content of the page. Of us according to the visitor's browser type and / or other information

**Copyright © Smoner** **2024**
